<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Sagar Bhujbal</title>
    <link>https://sagar2bhujbal.github.io/SB_portfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Sagar Bhujbal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sagar2bhujbal.github.io/SB_portfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 6: Sales Management using PowerBI</title>
      <link>https://sagar2bhujbal.github.io/SB_portfolio/post/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sagar2bhujbal.github.io/SB_portfolio/post/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>In this Project I have used sample database from Microsoft and extracted data required by problem statement using SQL queries.Extracted data further loaded into PowerBI for Dashboard. This project is consist of 4 steps:
 Business Request and User Stories Data Cleansing &amp;amp; Transformation(SQL) Data Model creation Dashboard  1. Business Request and User Stories :
The business request for this data analyst project was an executive sales report for sales managers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 5:Statistical Trend Analysis on Internet users in the UK</title>
      <link>https://sagar2bhujbal.github.io/SB_portfolio/post/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sagar2bhujbal.github.io/SB_portfolio/post/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>In this project, Data is taken from the office of the National Statistics website. This data is collected via survey by the Labour Force Survey. Due to COVID 19, there could be some impact on survey data since it was collected just before the pandemic breaks in. As per ONS department survey analysis further in data, there is larger than usual growth for the age group 75+, it could be due to pandemic and issues during survey collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 4:Stocks Market Time Series Analysis</title>
      <link>https://sagar2bhujbal.github.io/SB_portfolio/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sagar2bhujbal.github.io/SB_portfolio/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>In this Project I have studied four different random stock for analysing trend ,later also tried prediction on those stocks.For this task I have downloaded following four time series from Yahoo Finance for the period 1st Jan 2018 to 31st Dec 2020.
 Greggs plc (GRG) Allianz Technology Trust Plc (ATT ) NEXT plc ( NXT ) Just Eat Takeaway.com N.V (JET )
From this downloaded data I have used date and Close column (which indicates closing price of share for corresponding dates) for further processing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 3: Breast Cancer Classification and clustering</title>
      <link>https://sagar2bhujbal.github.io/SB_portfolio/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sagar2bhujbal.github.io/SB_portfolio/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>In this project,I aimed to create a computerised system which can classify two different (Bening and Malignant cases) using various classification methods and later also used clustering techniques. For this project data from following website is used.Link to repository
When primary analysis is done I found out that Data has total 32 attributes and outof which 30 attributes are real.There were 357 Benign and 212 malignant cases present in the data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Analysis of Armory in CS:GO</title>
      <link>https://sagar2bhujbal.github.io/SB_portfolio/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sagar2bhujbal.github.io/SB_portfolio/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>*AIM : To find the best features in CS:Go data that can predict win accurately.
*Idea : One question people always ask to win a team is “Tell us about the winning recipe?”. Is there a secret ingredient? .It’s all started with one simple question. How small decisions players make during a game will have an impact on a game. For example, this idea we will analyze the armory. How small decision like buying a weapon in a particular round has an impact on match or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Project Owl Image Processing</title>
      <link>https://sagar2bhujbal.github.io/SB_portfolio/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sagar2bhujbal.github.io/SB_portfolio/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>The aim of the project was to develop an image processing algorithm that would allow us to preprocess fundus images of eyes to highlight the various symptoms of diabetic retinopathy. The project concluded work for this semester with the development and implementation of algorithms to remove errors from the fundus images (such as reflection), highlight hard exudates and blood vessel proliferation. They were implemented using MATLAB. For future work, machine learning algorithms must be developed to be able to identify whether a patient suffers from diabetic retinopathy or to predict whether, in future, he will be afflicted by the same.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
